AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records on Microfilm 5478 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Sub-Series 22: 1922 Strike Files, 1922-1925
  - Series 22: 1922 Strike Files (Reel no.47) (Reel 87)
    - Denver and Salt Lake Railroad, 1922-1923; 1 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-165: June 21, 1922 - December 12, 1923
    - Houston and Brazos Valley Railroad, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-166: August 10, 1922 - May 15, 1923
    - Midland Terminal Railroad, 1922-1923; 3 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-167: August 18, 1922 - March 15, 1923
    - Stevens Point and Northern Railway, 1922; 4 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-168: August 17, 1922 - August 21, 1922
    - Texas and Mexico Railroad, 1922-1923; 5 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-169: August 23, 1922 - March 16, 1923
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad, 1922; 6 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-170: August 24, 1922 - October 16, 1922
    - Georgia, Florida and Alabama Railroad, 1922; 7 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-171: August 26, 1922 - October 16, 1922
    - Manufacturers Junction Railroad of Western Electric, 1922; 8 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-172: August 29, 1922 - September 1, 1922
    - Muscatine, Burlington and Southern Railroad, 1922-1923; 9 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-173: August 26, 1922 - May 11, 1923
    - Manufacturers Railway Co., 1922-1923; 10 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-174: September 1, 1922 - November 15, 1923
    - Camas Prairie Railroad, 1922-1923; 11 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-175: August 28, 1922 - April 3, 1923
    - West Virginia Northern Railroad, 1922-1923; 12 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-176: September 6, 1922 - April 6, 1923
    - Detroit, Toledo and Shore Line Railroad, 1922-1923; 13 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-177: September 8, 1922 - December 26, 1923
    - Mineral Point and Northern Railroad, 1922-1923; 14 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-178: September 13, 1922 - March 15, 1923
    - Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway, 1922-1923; 15 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-179: September 14, 1922 - April 5, 1923
    - Lake Superior and Ishpeming Railroad, 1922; 16 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-180: September 14, 1922 - October 21, 1922
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway, 1922-1923; 17 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-181: September 14, 1922 - March 26, 1923
    - Copper Range Railroad, 1922-1923; 18 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-182: September 14, 1922 - October 23, 1923
    - St. Paul Union Depot Company, 1922-1923; 19 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-183: September 14, 1922 - April 3, 1923
    - St. Paul Bridge and Terminal Company, 1922; 20 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-184: September 14, 1922 - October 21, 1922
    - Minnesota, Dakota and Western Railway, 1922-1923; 21 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-185: September 14, 1922 - April 5, 1923
    - Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad, 1922-1924; 22 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-186: September 16, 1922 - April 8, 1924
    - Union Stock Yards Railroad, 1922-1924; 23 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-187: September 14, 1922 - February 4, 1924
    - Western Alabama Railroad, 1922-1923; 24 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-188: September 18, 1922 - May 7, 1923
    - Ulster and Delaware Railroad, 1922-1923; 25 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-189: September 8, 1922 - May 25, 1923
    - Norfolk, Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad, 1922-1923; 26 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-190: September 21, 1922 - March 28, 1923
    - Boston Terminal Company, 1922-1923; 27 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-191: September 29, 1922 - December 3, 1923
    - Tonopah, Tide Water and Death Valley Railroad, 1922; 28 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-192: September 29, 1922 - October 12, 1922
    - Houston Belt Terminal Railroad, 1922; 29 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-193: October 11, 1922 - October 16, 1922
    - Duluth South Shore and Atlantic Railway, 1922; 30 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-194: October 12, 1922 - October 24, 1922
    - Sioux City Terminal Railway Company, 1922; 31 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-195: October 6, 1922 - October 18, 1922
    - Ft. Dodge, Des Moines, Southern Railroad, 1922; 32 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-196: October 23, 1922 - October 24, 1922
    - Quanah Acme and Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923; 33 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-197: November 13, 1922 - April 18, 1923
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1922-1923; 34 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-198: October 24, 1922 - July 11, 1923
    - New York, Philadelphia and Norfolk Railroad, 1922-1923; 35 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-199: December 11, 1922 - April 3, 1923
    - Galveston, Houston and Henderson and Galveston Wharf Company Railways, 1922-1923; 36 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-200: December 24, 1922 - March 14, 1923
    - Memphis Union Station Railroad, 1923; 37 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-201: January 20, 1923 - October 20, 1923
    - Blue Ridge Railroad, 1923; 38 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-203: April 18, 1923 - July 9, 1923
    - Morgan Engineering Company, 1922-1923; 39 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-204: November 15, 1922 - September 29, 1923
    - Waco, Beaumont, Trinity and Sabine Railway, 1923; 40 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-205: April 19, 1923 - April 24, 1923
    - Indianapolis Belt Railroad, 1922-1924; 41 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-206: March 1, 1923 - April 15, 1924
    - Dallas Terminal Railway, 1923; 42 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-207: May 11, 1923 - July 5, 1923
    - Savannah and Atlanta Railroad, 1923; 43 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-208: March 5, 1923 - October 18, 1923
    - Davenport Locomotive Works, 1923; 44 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-209: July 14, 1923 - August 3, 1923
    - Midland Valley Railroad, 1923; 45 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-210: September 30, 1922 - November 2, 1923
    - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau, 1923; 46 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-211: September 13, 1923 - October 3, 1923
    - Cleveland Crane and Engineering Company, 1923; 47 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-212: February 20, 1923 - October 25, 1923
    - Wrightsville and Tennille Railroad, 1923; 48 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-213: October 20, 1923 - December 11, 1923
    - Union Railroad, 1923; 49 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-214: November 2, 1923 - November 6, 1923
    - St. Louis Refrigerator Car Company, 1923; 50 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-215: November 19, 1923 - December 20, 1923
    - New Jersey, Indiana and Illinois Railroad, 1923; 51 (Reel 87)
      Code no. 3C-216: December 10, 1923 - December 14, 1923
- Sub-Series 25: Master File of Official Circulars, 1916-1961
  Reels 88-111: Circular letters and newsletters the audience for which were individual unions affiliated with the RED. News items relate to federal legislation and rules changes, carrier initiatives, and to RED activities and those of the individual unions
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.1) (Reel 88)
    - Official Circulars pt.1: nos.27-39, 1917; 1 (Reel 88)
      March 16, 1917 - July 10, 1917
    - Official Circulars pt.1: nos.40-86, 1917-1918; 2 (Reel 88)
      July 16, 1917 - December 30, 1918
    - Official Circulars pt.2: nos.87-113, 1919; 3 (Reel 88)
      January 8, 1919 - November 15, 1919
    - Official Circulars pt.2: nos.114-121, 1919-1920; 4 (Reel 88)
      December 9, 1919 - June 17, 1920
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.2) (Reel 89)
    - Official Circulars pt.2: nos.122-127, 1920-1921; 1 (Reel 89)
      June 21, 1920 - January 6, 1921
    - Official Circulars pt.3: nos.128-129, 1921; 2 (Reel 89)
      January 12, 1921 - March 26, 1921
    - Official Circulars pt.3: no.130, 1921; 3 (Reel 89)
      March 31, 1921 - June 8, 1921
    - Official Circulars pt.3: no.131, 1921; 4 (Reel 89)
      June 15, 1921 - September 26, 1921
    - Official Circulars pt.3: nos.132-124, 1921; 5 (Reel 89)
      September 27, 1921 - December 3, 1921
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.3) (Reel 90)
    - Official Circulars pt.4: nos.135-136, 1922; 1 (Reel 90)
      January 4, 1922 - May 11, 1922
    - Official Circulars pt.4: unnumbered, 1922-1923; 2 (Reel 90)
      May 16, 1922 - April 30, 1923
    - Official Circulars pt.5: nos. 2-30, 1924-1926; 3 (Reel 90)
      August 9, 1924 - December 31, 1926
    - Official Circulars pt.5: unnumbered, 1927-1930; 4 (Reel 90)
      January 1, 1927 - December 31, 1930
    - Official Circulars pt.5: unnumbered, 1931; 5 (Reel 90)
      January 8, 1931 - December 30, 1931
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.4) (Reel 91)
    - Official Circulars pt.6: nos.1-2, 1932-1933; 1 (Reel 91)
      February 1, 1932 - August 30, 1933
    - Official Circulars pt.6: nos.3-17, 1933-1934; 2 (Reel 91)
      August 31, 1933 - April 4, 1934
    - Official Circulars pt.6: nos.18-83, 1934; 3 (Reel 91)
      April 11, 1934 - December 28, 1934
    - Official Circulars pt.7: nos.84-151, 1934-1935; 4 (Reel 91)
      December 27, 1934 - December 27, 1935
    - Official Circulars pt.8: nos.152-227, 1936; 5 (Reel 91)
      January 2, 1936 - June 24, 1936
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.5) (Reel 92)
    - Official Circulars pt.8: nos.228-289, 1936; 1 (Reel 92)
      July 1, 1936 - December 30, 1936
    - Official Circulars pt.9: nos.290-345, 1936-1937; 2 (Reel 92)
      December 30, 1936 - May 24, 1937
    - Official Circulars pt.9: nos.346-420, 1937; 3 (Reel 92)
      June 1, 1937 - December 30, 1937
    - Official Circulars pt.10: nos.421-487, 1938; 4 (Reel 92)
      January 3, 1938 - July 12, 1938
    - Official Circulars pt.10: nos.488-549, 1938; 5 (Reel 92)
      July 25, 1938 - December 30, 1938
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.6) (Reel 93)
    - Official Circulars pt.11: nos.550-600, 1939; 1 (Reel 93)
      January 10, 1939 - May 29, 1939
    - Official Circulars pt.11: nos.601-658, 1939; 2 (Reel 93)
      June 1, 1939 - December 26, 1939
    - Official Circulars pt.12: nos.659-719, 1940; 3 (Reel 93)
      January 2, 1940 - July 10, 1940
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.7) (Reel 94)
    - Official Circulars pt.12: nos.720-779, 1940; 1 (Reel 94)
      July 29, 1940 - December 30, 1940
    - Official Circulars pt.13: nos.780-809, 1941; 2 (Reel 94)
      January 6, 1941 - March 19, 1941
    - Official Circulars pt.13: nos.810-862, 1941; 3 (Reel 94)
      March 28, 1941 - April 18, 1941
    - Official Circulars pt.13: nos.863-912, 1941; 4 (Reel 94)
      April 14, 1941 - August 13, 1941
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.8) (Reel 95)
    - Official Circulars pt.13: nos.913-964, 1941; 1 (Reel 95)
      August 29, 1941 - December 23, 1941
    - Official Circulars pt.14: nos.966-988, 1942; 2 (Reel 95)
      January 6, 1942 - January 28, 1942
    - Official Circulars pt.14: nos.989-1032, 1942; 3 (Reel 95)
      February 9, 1942 - May 15, 1942
    - Official Circulars pt.14: nos.1033-1081-B, 1942; 4 (Reel 95)
      May 20, 1942 - August 25, 1942
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.9) (Reel 96)
    - Official Circulars pt.14: nos.1082-1150, 1942; 1 (Reel 96)
      September 8, 1942 - December 10, 1942
    - Official Circulars pt.15: nos.1151-1195, 1943; 2 (Reel 96)
      January 15, 1943 - May 14, 1943
    - Official Circulars pt.15: nos.1196-1250, 1943; 3 (Reel 96)
      May 24, 1943 - October 4, 1943
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.10) (Reel 97)
    - Official Circulars pt.15: nos.1251-1298, 1943; 1 (Reel 97)
      October 6, 1943 - December 21, 1943
    - Official Circulars pt.16: nos.1299-1317, 1944; 2 (Reel 97)
      January 3, 1944 - March 9, 1944
    - Official Circulars pt.16: nos.1318-1348A, 1944; 3 (Reel 97)
      March 20, 1944 - June 9, 1944
    - Official Circulars pt.16: nos.1348-11-1378, 1944; 4 (Reel 97)
      June 10, 1944 - December 28, 1944
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.11) (Reel 98)
    - Official Circulars pt.17: nos.1379-1402, 1945; 1 (Reel 98)
      February 5, 1945 - February 21, 1945
    - Official Circulars pt.17: nos.1402-1-1444, 1945; 2 (Reel 98)
      February 28, 1945 - August 20, 1945
    - Official Circulars pt.17: nos.1445-1476, 1945; 3 (Reel 98)
      September 18, 1945 - December 26, 1945
    - Official Circulars pt.18: nos.1447-1498, 1946; 4 (Reel 98)
      January 8, 1946 - December 14, 1946
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.12) (Reel 99)
    - Official Circulars pt.19: nos.1499-1535, 1947; 1 (Reel 99)
      January 14, 1947 - August 11, 1947
    - Official Circulars pt.19: nos.1536-1579, 1947; 2 (Reel 99)
      August 11, 1947 - September 15, 1947
    - Official Circulars pt.19: nos.1580-1603, 1947; 3 (Reel 99)
      September 15, 1947 - December 10, 1947
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.13) (Reel 100)
    - Official Circulars pt.20: nos.1604-1641-P, 1948-1949; 1 (Reel 100)
      January 28, 1948 - March 21, 1949
    - Official Circulars pt.20: nos.1641-Q-1687, 1948-1949; 2 (Reel 100)
      April 8, 1948 - March 29, 1949
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.14) (Reel 101)
    - Official Circulars pt.21: nos.1688-1745, 1949; 1 (Reel 101)
      January 31, 1949 - December 15, 1949
    - Official Circulars pt.22: nos.1746-1785, 1950; 2 (Reel 101)
      January 10, 1950 - May 5, 1950
    - Official Circulars pt.22: nos.1786-1820, 1950; 3 (Reel 101)
      October 16, 1950 - December 26, 1950
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.15) (Reel 102)
    - Official Circulars pt.22-25: nos.1821-1823FF, 1940-1956; 1 (Reel 102)
      October 18, 1950 - June 26, 1956
    - Official Circulars pt.23: nos.1824-1856, 1951; 2 (Reel 102)
      January 31, 1951 - June 18, 1951
    - Official Circulars pt.23: nos.1857-1910, 1951; 3 (Reel 102)
      June 18, 1951 - December 28, 1951
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.16) (Reel 103)
    - Official Circulars pt.24: nos.1911-1944, 1952; 1 (Reel 103)
      January 2, 1952 - June 10, 1952
    - Official Circulars pt.24: nos.1945-1990, 1952; 2 (Reel 103)
      June 10, 1952 - December 22, 1952
    - Official Circulars pt.24: nos.1991-2010-24, 1953-1954; 3 (Reel 103)
      February 12, 1953 - September 15, 1954
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.17) (Reel 104)
    - Official Circulars pt.24: nos.2010-25-2010-38, 1954-1955; 1 (Reel 104)
      November 5, 1954 - April 13, 1955
    - Official Circulars pt.24: nos.2038-2074, 1953; 2 (Reel 104)
      June 30, 1953 - December 21, 1953
    - Official Circulars pt.25: nos.2074-1-2084, 1954; 3 (Reel 104)
      January 20, 1954 - March 12, 1954
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.18) (Reel 105)
    - Official Circulars pt.25: nos.2085-2127, 1954; 1 (Reel 105)
      January 20, 1954 - March 31, 1954
    - Official Circulars pt.25: nos.2128-2172, 1954; 2 (Reel 105)
      March 31, 1954 - September 30, 1954
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.19) (Reel 106)
    - Official Circulars pt.25:nos.2173-2217, 1954; 1 (Reel 106)
      September 30, 1954 - December 30, 1954
    - Official Circulars pt.26: nos.2010-39-2037, 1953-1955; 2 (Reel 106)
      June 30, 1953 - April 20, 1955
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.20) (Reel 107)
    - Official Circulars pt.26: nos.2219-2236, 1955; 1 (Reel 107)
      February 15, 1955 - April 22, 1955
    - Official Circulars pt.26-27: nos.2237-2268, 1955; 2 (Reel 107)
      April 22, 1955 - June 15, 1955
    - Official Circulars pt.27: nos.2269-2304-6, 1955; 3 (Reel 107)
      June 15, 1955 - December 22, 1955
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.21) (Reel 108)
    - Official Circulars pt.28: nos.2304-7-2336, 1955-1956; 1 (Reel 108)
      October 15, 1955 - January 11, 1956
    - Official Circulars pt.28: nos.2342-2357-9, 1955-1956; 2 (Reel 108)
      October 5, 1955 - December 12, 1956
    - Official Circulars pt.29: nos.2357-10-2357-30, 1956-1960; 3 (Reel 108)
      December 13, 1956 - November 17, 1960
    - Official Circulars pt.30: nos.2357-31-2357-46, 1961-1964; 4 (Reel 108)
      February 3, 1961 - March 17, 1964
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.22) (Reel 109)
    - Official Circulars pt.30:2358-2374, 1956-1957; 1 (Reel 109)
      August 27, 1956 - August 28, 1957
    - Official Circulars pt.30: nos.2375-2379, 1958; 2 (Reel 109)
      March 11, 1958 - May 6, 1958
    - Official Circulars pt.30-31: nos.2380-2400-6, 1958-1960; 3 (Reel 109)
      May 23, 1958 - March 15, 1960
    - Official Circulars pt.31: nos.2401-2408-8, 1959-1960; 4 (Reel 109)
      June 19, 1959 - September 6, 1960
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.23) (Reel 110)
    - Official Circulars pt.31: nos.2409-2430, 1959-1960; 1 (Reel 110)
      August 26, 1959 - November 16, 1960
    - Official Circulars pt.32-34: nos.2431-2449, 1961-1962; 2 (Reel 110)
      January 20, 1961 - April 13, 1962
    - Official Circulars pt.34: nos.2450-2463-6, 1962; 3 (Reel 110)
      April 24, 1962 - December 27, 1962
    - Official Circulars pt.35-36: nos.2463-7-2463-22, 1962-1964; 4 (Reel 110)
      January 29, 1963 - October 7, 1964
  - Series 25: Official Circulars Master File, 1916-1962 (Reel no.24) (Reel 111)
    - Official Circulars pt.36-37: nos.2463-23-2470-15, 1964-1966; 1 (Reel 111)
      October 7, 1964 - July 1, 1966
    - Official Circulars pt.37-39: nos.4270-17-2504, 1967; 2 (Reel 111)
      February 2, 1967 - August 1, 1967